〜♪
Fireworks Festival
Good morning.
（日代(ひしろ)）おはようございます
（海崎(かいざき)）ん…
（海崎）あっ おはよう
Mornin'!
Not often that you start
a conversation.
珍しいね 日代さんから
声かけてくれるなんて
Is that so?
（日代）そうですか？
What are you grinning for?
何ですか？ ニヤニヤと
気持ち悪い
It's creepy.
きもっ？
Creepy?!
Huh?
あれ？ ヘアゴム 何か新しい？
Are those new hair ties?
Yes. Kariu-san and Tamarai-san
gave them to me.
はい 狩生(かりう)さんと玉来(たまらい)さんに
いただきました
As thanks for the other day.
先日のお礼だと
Seems like Hishiro-san's
starting to change, too.
（海崎）
ちょっとは 変わってきてんのかな
日代さんも…
Morning, Arata-kun!
（小野屋(おのや)）おっはよー 新太(あらた)くーん
An! Jeez!
杏(あん) お前…
Morning, Hishiro-san!
（小野屋）日代さんも おはよう
Good morning, four-eyed braid girl.
おはようございます
三つ編みメガネさん
I have a name. It's Onoya An.
小野屋 杏です
そろそろ 覚えてね 日代千鶴(ちづる)さん
Remember it already,
Hishiro Chizuru-san.
朝っぱらから
イラッとするほど元気ですね
It is far too early to be that hyper.
I have low blood pressure,
so honestly, I envy you.
私は低血圧なので
正直 しっとします
Whoa, even Hishiro-san
gets jealous sometimes!
へえ 日代さんでも
しっとすることがあるんだ
But is that really caused
by low blood pressure?
でも それって
本当に血圧のことなのかなあ？
Onoya-san! Good morning!
（夜明(よあけ)）小野屋さん
おはよう
（夜明）ちょっといいかな？
（小野屋）おわっ 何…
Got a minute?
What? Hey!
ちょっととととと…
Sorry, Hishiro-san!
ごめんね 日代さん
朝から うるさいのが邪魔して
For the loud interruption.
I'm gonna borrow her for a minute!
この人 ちょっと借りてくね
Okay...
（日代）はい…
（夜明）あははは
O-Ow! That hurts!
（夜明）ははは
（小野屋）ちょっと 痛いってば
放して！ あ！ あ…
Let go!
I think that's the first time
I've seen you talking to Yoake-kun.
（海崎）そう言えば
日代さんと夜明くんが—
話してるとこ見たの 初めてかも
結構 気軽な感じだったね
You know each other?
Ryo was in my class last year.
了(りょう)は去年 同じクラスだったので
"Ryo"?
ちょ… ちょっと待って
W-Wait, you call Yoake-kun "Ryo"?
夜明君のこと“了”って
呼んでんの？
Yes.
はい そう呼んでと言われたので
He asked me to.
へえ
You're pretty close, huh?
仲 いいじゃん
Are we?
（日代）そうですか？
Wait. Don't jump to conclusions.
（海崎）いや
仲がいいってわけでもないのか？
大神(おおが)のことも言われるまま
“カズ君”って呼んでたし…
She calls Oga "Kazu-kun" like he told her to.
But...
でも…
Ryo
Kazu-kun
What's with this difference?
この差
Kaizaki-san
I can't accept this!
何か納得いかねえ！
Th-Then call me Arata—
じゃ じゃあ俺のことも 新太…
Sorry. Never mind.
ごめん 何でもない…
Why?
（海崎）何を… 呼び方１つで
It's just a name.
Double Panic
How old am I?
ガキか
（海崎）うーん 夏休みかあ
Summer vacation!
（大神）
メチャメチャうれしそうだね
You look super happy.
そりゃうれしいさあ
Damn straight I am!
These long vacations are to be treasured!
（海崎）
貴重すぎだよ こんな大型連休
ありがたみ 分かってんのかねえ
学生諸君
Do you even get that, young students?
Oh yeah, Arata. You had to take
make-ups after the finals, too.
そういえば 新太
期末も再試になってたけど
あれ 合格したの？
Have you passed them yet?
Huh?
ん？ いや してねえけど
No, not yet.
Then you'll be doing make-ups
during summer vacation, too.
じゃあ夏休み中も頑張ってね 再試
はあ？ 夏休み中も あんのかよ！
Even during summer vacation?!
って聞いたよ？
So I hear.
I've never had to take one myself.
俺 なったことないから
知らないけど
But I've been taking make-ups
the entire first term...
俺 １学期の間も
ずうっと—
再試 再試
再試だったのに…
（狩生）まあ 自業自得よね
You reap what you sow.
I'll be coming to prep for entrance exams.
俺も受験対策で—
（大神）来るからさあ
（狩生）えっ
昼は一緒に食べよ
Let's eat lunch together.
Entrance exams?
受験対策？
Oga, you're going to some other college?
大神 外部の大学 受けるの？
Hmm...
うーん 一応はこのまま
附属の青葉(あおば)大で考えてるけど—
I'm still considering just going on
to Aoba University,
but I'd like to keep my options open,
まあ 選択肢は
広げておきたいし—
センター受験コースも
取っとこうかなって
so I'm gonna take the
Center Exam Prep Course.
そう… なんだ あ…
Oh, I see...
Okay, homeroom's starting.
（天津(あまつ)）はーい
ホームルーム 始めるよー
Oga-kun, Hishiro-san.
（天津）大神くん 日代さん
１学期 委員長 お疲れさまでした
A big hand for our first-term class reps.
Oh.
（海崎）そっか
夜明さんも言ってたっけ
Yoake-san mentioned this high school
was affiliated to a college.
この高校は 附属の大学があるって
Guess most of them go there.
だいたいの子は
そこに行く感じなのかな
いいなあ
みんな 大学でも一緒なのか
Lucky them.
They get to be together in college, too.
"Lucky them"? Come on.
（海崎）何だよ “いいな”って
It has nothing to do with me.
俺には関係ないだろ
（小野屋）では １学期が無事に
終わりましたことを 祝して—
So, to celebrate successfully
surviving the first term...
（小野屋）カンパーイ！
（一同）カンパーイ！
Cheers!
Again, how come we always
have to drink at my place?
だから 何で飲み会の会場が
俺ん家(ち) なんですかね？
Well, looking like this,
we can't go out to drink.
だって この姿じゃ
外では飲めないじゃないですか
お酒を買うことも できませんし
Can't even buy booze!
But here, we can get the lab to deliver it!
その点 海崎さんちなら—
頼めば研究所から
届けてもらえますし
And we can expense it all!
（夜明･小野屋）
何と言っても 経費で飲める！
Such horrible grown-ups!
（海崎）嫌な大人たちだ
Oh, sorry.
あっ すみません
早いうちに 夏休みの予定を
確認しておきたいんですが
We'd like to know your summer
vacation plans as soon as possible,
but you don't have any, right?
予定も何も
毎週 再試なんですから—
You're too busy taking make-ups
to even visit your family!
実家にも 帰れませんよねえ
夏休み中に
合格できるんですかねえ？
Can you pass before the vacation ends?
（夜明･小野屋）あっはっはっはっ
（海崎）お前ら…
You two...
Anyway, if you do go anywhere,
let us know ahead of time.
まあ どこかに出かける時は
事前に連絡ください
It may be a vacation,
but we still have to observe.
休日とは言え
観察義務が ありますので
分かってるよ
I know.
That said, Onoya and I will be
joining in summer school,
（夜明）とは言え 僕と小野屋も
補習に参加するので—
学校で会えるんですけどね
so we'll see you there.
えっ そうなのか？
Oh? You will?
違和感なく 高校生やれるよう—
Part of our job is studying furiously
so we can convincingly act like students.
勉学に励むのも
仕事のうちですから
ふーん 大神にしても
夜明さんたちにしても—
First Oga, now you two.
Lots of ways to handle summer vacation.
休みなのに いろいろあるんだな
Oh, yeah! Speaking of Oga-kun!
（小野屋）
そうだ 大神君と言えば—
He really hasn't noticed, has he?
全然気づいてないんですかね？
狩生さんの気持ち
How Kariu-san feels.
ああ… そうみたいだな
Apparently not.
周りが 何とかしてやんねえと—
Unless the rest of us do something,
（海崎）絶対進展しねえぞ あの２人
（小野屋）うんうん
those two will never get anywhere.
ですよねえ
I know!
We need to make Oga feel
some danger, you know?
大神には もっと危機感とか
与えたほうが いいんじゃねえの？
それだ！ よし 先輩
狩生さんに迫りましょう
That's it!
Okay, Senpai, go after Kariu-san!
大人の魅力で
With your adult charm!
何 言ってんの？
Listen to yourself.
If another guy gets close to
Kariu-san and tempts her,
狩生さんに男が近づいて
揺らぐのを見れば—
さすがの大賀君も 平常心じゃ
いられないってことですよ
even Oga would have to feel something!
（夜明）そもそもさ
（小野屋･海崎）ん？
You know...
狩生さんはともかく
大神君は どうなの？
Kariu-san is one thing,
but how does Oga-kun feel?
Is this really something we should be
getting worked up about?
勝手に 周りが盛り上がって
大丈夫なの？
We're all old enough
いい大人なんだから—
悪ノリで 思春期の
学生の心を振り回さないこと
to know better than to toy
with the hearts of children.
What is this sadist talking about?
やだー ドＳが何か言ってる〜
さんざん俺を振り回すくせに—
After all the time he's spent
toying with my heart?
どの口が… やだ〜
No way.
（夜明）この酔っ払いが！
You drunkards.
What about you, Kaizaki-san?
（夜明）海崎さんこそ
どうなんです？ その辺
There's no helping those who are
as innocent as Kariu-san.
狩生さんたちのように—
初々しすぎると
面倒 見きれませんが—
But there's no reason you couldn't
have something like that.
海崎さんにも そういう話が
あってよいのでは と
Get myself a high school girlfriend?
女子高生の彼女 作れっての？
ははっ 冗談だろ
Ha! What a joke.
（夜明）
それも ありなんじゃないですか？
There's no reason you couldn't.
A one-year, limited edition of youth.
１年限定の青春
どうせ 忘れられてしまう幻…
なんですし
You're an illusion.
They'll forget you, anyway.
I know.
そんなの—
You don't need to remind me.
今さら言われなくても
承知してるよ
Arata! Sorry I'm late.
新太 お待たせー お昼食べよ
Lunch time?
It's kinda unusual to see you
bring lunch from home.
大神が弁当って 何か新鮮だな
（大神）
学食が開いてないからね
The cafeteria's closed.
I make one for my dad every day,
父さんのは 毎日作ってるから—
so I just double up during holidays.
休みの間は 自分のも一緒にね
Huh? You made that?
え？ その弁当 大神が作ったの？
Yeah. I cook a lot.
うん 俺 結構料理する
すげえ 意外 マジかよ
Really? I seriously didn't expect that.
Falling for me yet?
惚れるっしょー？
Totally...
惚れるわ〜
So, how'd the make-ups go?
で どうだったの？ 再試は
（海崎）ん ダメだった
I failed them.
（大神）ですよねー
（海崎）うるせっ
Thought so.
Shut up!
Kariu-san is one thing,
but how does Oga-kun feel?
（夜明）狩生さんはともかく
大神君は どうなの？
Say, Oga...
（海崎）
そう言えば 大神ってさ—
I've never heard any rumors
about your love life.
浮いた話 全然聞かないよな
（大神）ん？
（海崎）いや ん？ じゃなくて
Hm?
No, not "hm."
今まで 女の子と
つきあったこと とかは？ あんの？
You ever dated a girl before?
は？ ないよ 何 急に
Huh? No! Where'd this come from?
Any ask you out?
（海崎）告られたことは？
うっ… は あるけど…
Um... yeah.
つきあわなかったの？
And you said no?
ううう… って
何なの？ さっきから
But seriously, what is this?!
Oh...
いやあ 今 好きな子とか
いねえのかなって思って
I was just wondering
if there's anyone you like.
Anyone I like?
好きな子…
I like everyone!
みんな 好きだよ
What kinda answer is that?!
何だよ その答え
頭 どうなってんだ
What's wrong with your head?
新太に
頭どうこう言われたくないよ
My head's better than yours any day!
今 明らかに
恋のお話をしてただろうがよ 恋の
We are clearly talking about love! Romance!
何で そこで
キョトン顔なんだよ！
Why do you look baffled?!
（海崎）はあ… じゃあ例えば—
Okay, for example...
Like, someone you always
find yourself with, or...
気づけばいつも
一緒にいるなって子とか
ああ 女子な 女子
Oh, a girl, a girl.
ん？ おもしろい子だな
楽しいなとか
And you go, "She's interesting."
"She's fun."
You can talk about anything.
（海崎）何でも言い合えるな とか
（大神）うん
You don't want anyone taking her away.
（海崎）誰かに取られたら—
（海崎）嫌だなとか
（大神）う
You wanna hold hands.
（海崎）手をつなぎたいなとか
（大神）う
（海崎）キスしたいなとか
You wanna kiss her.
Maybe go all the way?
（海崎）その先もしたいな とか
そんなふうに見たことなんか
ないよ！
I've never looked at anyone like that!
例え話だよ
I was speaking hypothetically.
そういう子は いねえのか？ って
Asking if you had anyone like that.
Okay, okay.
まあまあ 勉強も大事だけど—
Studying's important,
but I think love is, too.
恋愛ってのも大事だと思うぞ
It's the last summer of high school.
高校最後の夏 二度と来ない
貴重な時間なんだから
It's a precious time that won't come again.
Before you know it, you'll be
the only single guy you know!
気づいたら将来 仲間内で—
独り身は自分だけと
いうことに… ひっ
どうしたの？ 大丈夫？
What's wrong? You okay?
I self-destructed.
（海崎）自爆しました 胸が痛い
My chest hurts.
Arata...
（大神）新太は… その…
Have you...
...ever done it?
したことあるの？
You know,
そういう… キス… とか
like, kissed a girl?
ふふん
I have.
あるよ
ぎっ バカのくせに
Even though you're dumb?!
おい バカは関係ねえだろ
Hey! What's that got to do with it?
（大神）新太のくせに
But it's you!
根本から否定すんな 俺の親に謝れ
Don't reject my very being!
Apologize to my parents.
（大神）ハレンチ！
That's so naughty!
（海崎）お前 ホントに
今どきの高校生か？
Are you really a modern high school boy?
（大神）スケベ！
（海崎）おいっ
Dirty!
Hey!
English Pop Quiz - 50 minutes
Studying's important,
but I think love is, too.
（海崎）勉強も大事だけど—
恋愛も大事だと思うぞ
It's the last summer of high school.
高校最後の夏 二度と来ない
貴重な時間なんだから
It's a precious time that won't come again.
"Won't come again"? That's every summer.
（大神）二度と来ないのは
いつの夏だって一緒だろ バカ
Idiot.
You wanna hold hands.
手をつなぎたいなとか
キスしたいなとか
You wanna kiss her.
（大神）
そんなふうに 見たことないよ
I've never looked at anyone like that.
Ever.
ないよ…
Argh...
（海崎）あーあ 結局ほとんど
１日つぶれてんじゃねえか
I ended up wasting
almost the whole day!
Vacation: Ruined.
夏休みの意味ねえ
But it's still a lot easier than
attending an exam school.
（大神）でも
予備校に行くことと比べたら—
まだ全然 余裕あるでしょ
（海崎）うわ 余裕とか
言いやがった ムカつく
You call this easy? You really know
how to get on my nerves.
Oh, man!
くそっ マジで 頭 痛え
My head hurts.
ちょっ いきなり何…
What the heck?
（大神）狩生が
（海崎）え？
Kariu!
Kariu and...
（海崎）狩生と… あっ！
あっ う！ くっうう
It's that new guy?!
（海崎）こ 後輩君じゃねえか
Why?!
何で？
If anyone finds out about ReLIFE,
（夜明）リライフがバレたら—
実験は終了ですよ
the experiment ends.
（大神）
う… 狩生 どうしたんだろう
What's Kariu doing?
He's not a student!
相手 学生じゃないし—
なんか 怖いし—
And he's kinda scary!
It's not some sort of hookup site thing?
まさか出会い系とか
そういうトラブルに？
（海崎）か… 狩生に限って
それは ねえだろ
K-Kariu, of all people,
would never do that.
I don't think he's up to
anything that creepy, either.
相手もたぶん—
そんな危ない感じでは
ないと思うかなあ なんて…
（大神）ああっ
車に乗せようとしてる！
He's trying to get her in his car!
What now? He's kidnapping her!
どうしよう
どこか連れていかれるんじゃ
（海崎）いやあ
それはねえと思うんだけど…
N-No, I really don't think so...
But what are they doing?
しかし ホント何なんだ あの２人
This clearly isn't any kind of date.
まさか デートってわけでも
なさそうだし…
Kariu's resisting.
（大神）狩生 嫌がってる
Kariu!
（大神）狩生！
（狩生）あっ え？ 大神？
Oga?!
（海崎）おおい
何 勝手に飛び出してんの？
Hey! Why did you just run out?!
た た 頼むから
俺の名前 呼ぶなよ！
P-P-Please, don't call my name!
巻き込むなよ！
Don't get me mixed up in this!
Um...
（上岡(かみおか)）ええっと… 彼氏さん？
Your boyfriend?
違います！ クラスの友達です
No! A friend from class!
What?
何？ 大神 何してんの？
What are you doing here, Oga?
（大神）補習の帰りだよ
そっちこそ 何してんの？
Coming home from exam prep.
What about you?
え？ あ いや その…
Um... well...
Oh, I see.
（上岡）そっか お友達か
A friend!
Perfect timing!
それは ちょうどよかった
This girl's got a touch of heat stroke.
（上岡）この子 ちょっと—
熱中症っぽく
なっちゃったみたいでね
I just happened to pass by.
そこに俺が通りかかって…
熱中症？
Heat... stroke?
I asked if she wanted me
to call an ambulance,
（上岡）救急車呼ぼうかって
聞いたんだけど—
そこまでじゃないってことで
but she said it wasn't that bad.
So I took her somewhere cool
and got her a drink,
とりあえず涼しいところで
水分を取ったら—
だいぶ 落ち着いたみたい
and she's doing better.
（海崎）
はあ… そんなこったろうと思った
That's pretty much what I thought.
で この暑さの中—
And given how hot it is,
I didn't wanna let her walk off alone,
また１人で歩かせるのも怖いし—
so I offered to drop her at the station.
駅まで送ろうかって
言ったんだけど—
But obviously she doesn't want
to get into a strange man's car.
さすがに知らない男の車に
乗りたくないよなあって—
We were at an impasse.
困ってたんだ
Well? Can I leave you with him, then?
どうしよう
もう彼に任せて大丈夫かな？
Uh... yeah...
（狩生）あ はい
Bye!
（上岡）じゃ 若いからって
暑さナメちゃダメだよ
Just 'cause you're young,
don't take the heat lightly.
Careful!
気をつけてね
Thank you.
（狩生）ありがとうございました
What a gentleman!
（大神）めっちゃ紳士
I heard all that.
Looks like things are gonna work out,
so I'm going home.
Walk Kariu home, okay?
He went home?!
（大神）帰っちゃったの？
（狩生）大神？
Oga?
あ ホントにもう大丈夫？
Are you really okay?
Yeah.
I'll walk you to the station.
駅まで送るよ
I'm headed home, too.
俺も ちょうど帰るとこだったし
（狩生）あ 大神
（大神）ん？
Oga...
あ… その…
Um...
Thanks for, uh, worrying about me.
心配してくれて
どうも ありがとうございました
何？
What?
You're being so sincere today
that it's kinda weird.
今日の狩生 素直すぎて
ちょっと不気味
（狩生）うっ
（大神）痛い！
Ow!
不気味って！
Weird?!
You picked the worst timing to say that!
このタイミングで言われると
一番イラッとくるから！
（大神）ごめん 間違えた
何か間違えたね 俺
Sorry! I messed up!
I clearly messed up!
もうっ
Jeez!
What? Why are you laughing
after I hit you?
何よ！ 何ぶたれて
笑ってんの？ 怖いんだけど
You're scaring me!
No, I just thought, we're always like this.
いや いつもどおりだなあ
この感じ と思って
It's fun.
楽しくて
Oh, really. Glad you're enjoying yourself.
あっそ 楽しそうで何より！
I was just wondering
if there's anyone you like.
（海崎）今 好きな子とか
いねえのかな って思って
You don't want anyone taking her away.
誰かに取られたら
嫌だなとか
You wanna hold hands.
手をつなぎたいなとか
It's the last summer of high school.
（海崎）高校最後の夏
二度と来ない
貴重な時間なんだから…
It's a precious time that won't come again.
（夜明）１年限定の青春…
A one-year, limited edition of youth.
どうせ忘れられてしまう幻…
なんですし
You're an illusion.
They'll forget you, anyway.
What do I do, Arata?
I'm in love with Kariu.
き… 来たあああっ！
I-It's happening!
When I was walking Kariu to the station,
I wanted to hold her hand.
狩生を駅まで送る時に—
手をつなぎたいなって
思ってしまって 自覚しました
That's how I realized.
へえ ほお
その顔 やめろよ！
Stop giving me that look!
いや… ニヤニヤが止まんない
Sorry, I can't stop smiling.
変態！
Creep!
Listen up, Oga.
いいか 大神
気づいちまったんなら—
Now that you've noticed,
you've gotta be a man and take action.
こういう時は
男からバシッと決めるもんだ
There's a fireworks festival soon, right?
今度 花火大会があるだろ？
Fireworks Festival
Invite her to it, and fess up.
あれに誘って 告れば？
Fess up?
告るって… 狩生に
“好きです”って 言うってこと？
You mean tell Kariu I love her?
当たり前だろ
ほかに 何 言う気だよ
Of course.
What else would you tell her?
She'd punch me!
殴られそう
そうかもな でも いいのか？
Yeah, maybe.
But are you okay with dawdling about?
Someone else might claim her.
ボヤボヤしてるうちに—
狩生が ほかの誰かに
取られちまっても
No...
嫌 だ…
（海崎）あっはあ
（大神）だから その顔 やめろ！
Please, stop doing that!
A confession?
告白… ですね
Ah, youth!
青春だね〜
When did you all get here?!
（大神）って いつの間に！
Well, we thought you could use
a young girl's point of view.
ほら 女子の意見も
あったほうがいいと思って
"Young" girl?
Uselessly dense
Tag-along
But even if I do wanna confess,
（大神）
でも 告るって言ってもさ—
I just don't know where to begin.
どうしたらいいか
全然 分かんないよ
An-chan, how would you like a boy
to confess his feelings?
杏ちゃんだったら どんなふうに
告白されたらうれしい？
ええ？ 気持ちがこもってれば
どんなのでもいいよ
As long as he puts his heart into it,
it really doesn't matter.
Hishiro-san?
日代さんは？
Sorry.
すみません そういうのは
経験がないので 分かりません
I have no experience with these things,
so I don't know.
（大神）そっか…
I see...
夜明君なら どう告る？
Yoake-kun, how would you do it?
何か大人っぽいし
すごい 参考になりそう
You seem so grown-up,
I'm sure you'd make for a great reference.
うーん 俺もまだ—
I've never done it, either.
Don't really know.
そういう経験なくて
分かんないや ごめんね
Sorry!
（小野屋･海崎）ぬう…
じゃあ 新太は？
Then... Arata?
今までの子たち
どうやって 口説いたの？
How'd you lure all your girls?
経験豊富なんでしょ？
You've had lots, right?
うっ 豊富とまでは言ってねえだろ
I did not say that.
いいや 今までの
余裕な感じからして—
No, you're so relaxed around them.
絶対 女の子慣れしてるよね？
You've known a lot of girls.
普通だっつの
That's normal!
（日代）へえ…
（海崎･大神）ん？
Kaizaki-san has a lot of
experience with women?
（日代）海崎さんは 女性経験が
豊富でいらっしゃるんですか？
How grown-up.
大人ですね
あ いや 普通だよ？
もう高３だしね
No, it's normal!
We're in third year!
それはそれは すみません
私が異常で
Well, I apologize for being abnormal.
あ そうじゃなくて
Not what I meant!
（海崎）笑ってんじゃねえぞ
助けろよ サポート課
Stop smiling and help me out here,
you support people!
Y-Yoake-kun, surely you've asked
someone out or been asked out!
（海崎）よ… 夜明君こそ—
告白くらい したり されたり
あんだろ？ 18にもなって
You're eighteen, right?
（夜明）まだ17です
I'm still seventeen!
そういうことじゃなくて…
That's beside the point!
（日代）
ええ そうですよね
ええ でも新太君の口説き文句
聞きたいけどなあ
But I bet Arata-kun's
pick-up lines are great!
I see. I really am abnormal.
私が異常なんです
（夜明）聞きたいなあ
（海崎）ちょっ
You've gotta tell me! I need help here!
I'm sorry I'm so abnormal.
異常ですみませんね
普通の海崎さん
（夜明）参考にさせてほしい
異常ですみませんね
普通の海崎さん
（海崎）やめろよ
Stop!
Fine, okay.
よし 分かった 決めた
I've made up my mind.
I'll invite Kariu to
the fireworks festival...
（大神）
俺 狩生を花火大会に誘って—
...and confess!
告白する！
Kariu, are you free on the 10th?
Wanna go to the
fireworks festival together?
（狩生）えっ！ 何これ？
何これ何これ
What?! What the hell is this?!
Did he send it to the wrong person?
誰かに 送り間違えた？
No, it says "Kariu"...
いや でも 狩生って
入ってるし 何で？
Why?
と とりあえず
ほのかと一緒に相談…
A-Anyway, I'd better see
what Honoka and Hishiro think...
It seems Oga just invited me
to the fireworks festival.
なんか大神から
花火大会の誘いが来たんだけど
I got it, too! Sounds like fun!
I got one, too.
I've been doing homework
and studying all summer,
so it'll be nice to take a breather.
He sent it to everyone...
（狩生）みんなに送ったんだ…
舞い上がって あたしのバカ…
I got all worked up for nothing...
But sure, why not?
でも まあいいや全然
That's just like Oga.
そういうとこが 大神らしい
I got one, too.
I've been doing homework and studying all summer,
so it'll be nice to take a breather.
Are you gonna wear a yukata, Hishiron?
〜♪
I don't have one.
Are you gonna wear a yukata, Hishiron?
Then let's go shopping together!
I was thinking of getting a new one myself.
NEXT EPISODE
（海崎）
日代さんって 緑 好きなの？
Hishiro, do you like green?
（日代）まあ 海崎さんは
地味な色がお好きなんですか？
Yeah. You like drab colors, Kaizaki-san?
（海崎）地味って…
Drab? I guess I own a lot of dark colors.
確かに黒っぽい服 多いけど…
Oh, but I like bright colors, too. Red, or...
（海崎）
あ… 明るい色も好きだよ 赤とか
Confession
（日代）参考にします
I'll keep that in mind.
（海崎）はっ？ 何の？
Huh? What for?